Guide to the Sara Hickman collection, 1978-2017 MS 718
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Audio and Video, 1980-2014
  - Sub-Series E: CDs
    - "The Best of Times: Texas Artists Performing the Music of Sara Hickman", 2011 (Box 7)
      These files are digitized master copy WAVs and access copy MP3s. Tracks include: Willie Nelson - "Simply," Patrice Pike - "Woman Waiting to Happen," Graham Wilkinson - "Two Days Today," Andrew Perry - "E Cosi Desio Me Mena," Ray Von Foster - "Give It Every Little Thing You've Got," After Math - "Larger Than Life," LZ Love - "I Couldn't Help Myself," The Nauer-Neverly Bros. - "False Pretenses," David Garza with Todd Wolfson - "Risk," Gretchen Phillips and Rob Halverson - "Tiny Movies," Colin Gilmore - "After the Fall," Rhett Miller - "Last Night Was a Big Rain," Elizabeth Wills - "Eye of the Storm," Shelley King - "Open up to Me," Marcia Ball - "Strong Woman," Trish Murphy with Charlie Sexton - "The Best of Times," The Djembabes - "It's in the Water," Christine Albert and Chris Gage - "Take Me with You," Robert Earl Keen - "Under the Sycamore Tree," Edie Brickell and New Bohemians - "Shadowboxing," Abra Moore - "Dear Tracey," Jimmy LaFave - "Standing Ground," Sarah Fox and Joel Guzman - "I Wear the Crown," The Flatlanders - "Comfort's Sigh," Betty Soo - "Sister and Sam," Ana Egge - "Joy," White Ghost Shivers - "Kayaking," Trout Fishing in America - "The Place Where the Garage Used to Stand," Darden Smith - "No Name for Love," Shawn Colvin - "Time Will Tell," Jess Klein - "The One," The Daze - "Hey Where You Goin'," Joe McDermott - "The Very Thing," Suzanna Choffel - "Matter of Time," Ruthie Foster - "Look at It This Way," The Sutcliffes - "Too Fast," Matt the Electrician - "Middle of a LIttle Country Road," Brave Combo - "Simply"
    - "Newborn, Too", 2014 (Box 7)
      These files are digitized master copy WAVs and access copy MP3s. Tracks include: "Welcome Home," "Mother Earth Father Time," "All the Pretty Little Horses," "Dream Life," "Edelweiss," "Moon Lullaby," "The Sky Is Gone," "You Remind Me," "Beautiful Boy," "Never Never Land," "Circle of Love," "Family Tree," "Goodnight My Angel"
- Series VI: Memorabilia, 1980s-2016
  - 40 reasons to love Sara Hickman box, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Awards - plaques and pottery, 1992-2016 (Box 8)
  - Buttons, 1990s (Box 8)
  - Concert passes, 1980s-2010s (Box 8)
  - "Necessary Angels" bracelet, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Super Pal Universe bag, 2007 (Box 8)
- Series VII: Oversize materials, 1985-2010s
  - Album art, 1990-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Dallas Observer" Music Awards ballot, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Fan mail, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Posters, 1980s-2010s (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Teaching materials, 2000s (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Three on a Hill" music video storyboard, ca. 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Billy Bragg / Sara Hickman poster, 1995-10-25 (Map-drawer 196, Item 29)
- Series VIII: Oral history, 2017
  - Sara Hickman oral history, 2018-07-31; 0.592 Gigabytes
    These born digital audio files consist of one master copy wav and one access copy mp3 located at scholarship.rice.edu.